https://printbox.com/printbox_privacy_policy.php

PrintBox Privacy Policy
Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the printbox.com and PrintBox Technologies Ltd. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to PrintBox Technologies Ltd. include printbox.com, The PrintBox Group, diy-tickets.com and worldforms.net. The PrintBox Group website is a ecommerce site. By using the PrintBox Group website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.
Collection of your Personal Information
The PrintBox Group may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase The PrintBox Group's products and services, we collect billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future.
Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by The PrintBox Group. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the PrintBox Group website.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through The PrintBox Group's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.
The PrintBox Group encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from The PrintBox Group so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. The PrintBox Group is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the PrintBox Group website.
Use of your Personal Information
The PrintBox Group collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested.
The PrintBox Group may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The PrintBox Group and its affiliates. The PrintBox Group may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
The PrintBox Group does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties.
The PrintBox Group may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The PrintBox Group, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
The PrintBox Group will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The PrintBox Group or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The PrintBox Group; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The PrintBox Group, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The PrintBox Group website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize The PrintBox Group pages, or register with The PrintBox Group site or services, a cookie helps The PrintBox Group to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same The PrintBox Group website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the PrintBox Group features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the PrintBox Group services or websites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
To secure your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure, The PrintBox Group uses the following:
Comodo.
When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol.
Comodo is an independent, third-party company engaged in the development of digital trust. Comodo provides authentication of Internet services, digital identity and intellectual property. By clicking on the Comodo logo, the Comodo website will serve up a web page that confirms that The PrintBox Group is verified by COMODO RSA Certification Authority.
Children Under Thirteen
The PrintBox Group does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.
Disconnecting your The PrintBox Group Account from Third Party Websites
You will be able to connect your The PrintBox Group account to third party accounts. BY CONNECTING YOUR THE PRINTBOX GROUP ACCOUNT TO YOUR THIRD PARTY ACCOUNT, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT YOU ARE CONSENTING TO THE CONTINUOUS RELEASE OF INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO OTHERS (IN ACCORDANCE WITH YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS ON THOSE THIRD PARTY SITES). IF YOU DO NOT WANT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU, INCLUDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION, TO BE SHARED INTHIS MANNER, DO NOT USE THE THIS FEATURE. You may disconnect your account from a third party account at any time. contact us via email or telephone.
Opt-Out & Unsubscribe
We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from The PrintBox Group by contacting us here:
- Web page: _________________
- Email: _________________
- Phone: _________________
Changes to this Statement
The PrintBox Group will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The PrintBox Group encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how The PrintBox Group is protecting your information.
Contact Information
The PrintBox Group welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The PrintBox Group has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The PrintBox Group at:
PrintBox Technologies Ltd.
7733 So Saginaw Ave
hicago, Illinois 60649
Email Address:
support@printbox.com
Telephone number:
(773) 734-6858
Effective as of December 02, 2016
